[
    {
        "question": "One should take care of old people",
        "words": {
          "4": "care",
          "1": "by",
          "3": "should",
          "2": "old",
          "5": "be",
          "6": "of",
          "7": "people",
          "8": "taken"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,3,5,8,4,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The policeman chased after the thief",
        "words": {
          "4": "policeman",
          "1": "being",
          "3": "thief",
          "2": "after",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "was",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "been",
          "9": "the",
          "10": "chased"
        },
        "answers":[[9,3,6,10,2,7,5,4],[5,3,6,10,2,7,9,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The guardians will speak to the teacher on this matter",
        "words": {
          "4": "teacher",
          "1": "guardians",
          "3": "matter",
          "2": "be",
          "5": "spoke",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "to",
          "8": "this",
          "9": "will",
          "10": "by",
          "11": "spoken",
          "12": "the",
          "13": "on"
        },
        "answers":[[12,4,9,2,11,7,10,6,1,13,8,3],[6,4,9,2,11,7,10,12,1,13,8,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bhagat Singh died for his country",
        "words": {
          "4": "Bhagat Singh",
          "1": "for",
          "3": "was",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "by",
          "6": "died",
          "7": "country"
        },
        "answers":[[]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rubaiya jumped onto the thief and caught it",
        "words": {
          "4": "thief",
          "1": "Rubaiya",
          "3": "and",
          "2": "jumped",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "was",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "been",
          "9": "caught",
          "10": "onto",
          "11": "was"
        },
        "answers":[[5,4,11,2,10,7,1,3,6,9],[5,4,6,2,10,7,1,3,11,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "We know that you are a cheat",
        "words": {
          "4": "known",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "cheat",
          "2": "us",
          "5": "you",
          "6": "it",
          "7": "a",
          "8": "to",
          "9": "by",
          "10": "are",
          "11": "is"
        },
        "answers":[[6,11,4,8,2,1,5,10,7,3],[1,5,10,7,3,11,4,8,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "All want money, but some get it",
        "words": {
          "4": "by some",
          "1": "by all",
          "3": "want",
          "2": "got",
          "5": "money",
          "6": "but",
          "7": "wanted",
          "8": "is",
          "9": "is"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,7,1,6,8,2,4],[5,8,7,1,6,9,2,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jewel's boss was telling him that she did not like his work style",
        "words": {
          "4": "his boss",
          "1": "by her",
          "3": "his work",
          "2": "Jewel",
          "5": "being",
          "6": "was",
          "7": "not",
          "8": "style",
          "9": "been",
          "10": "told",
          "11": "liked",
          "12": "was",
          "13": "by",
          "14": "that",
          "15": "did",
          "16": "she",
          "17": "like"
        },
        "answers":[[2,6,5,10,13,4,14,3,8,12,7,11,1],[2,12,5,10,13,4,14,3,8,6,7,11,1],[2,6,5,10,13,4,14,16,15,7,17,3,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The teacher has told the students that cow eats grass",
        "words": {
          "4": "grass",
          "1": "the teacher",
          "3": "cow",
          "2": "told",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "been",
          "7": "has",
          "8": "have",
          "9": "by",
          "10": "that",
          "11": "eats"
        },
        "answers":[[5,8,6,2,9,1,10,3,11,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "They had stolen all the gold before they set fire to the shop",
        "words": {
          "4": "the shop",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "set",
          "2": "stolen",
          "5": "fire",
          "6": "all",
          "7": "before",
          "8": "was",
          "9": "been",
          "10": "to",
          "11": "the gold",
          "12": "setted"
        },
        "answers":[[6,11,1,9,2,7,5,8,3,10,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nobody would have asked him any question if he knew what places he had to avoid",
        "words": {
          "4": "if",
          "1": "avoided",
          "3": "would",
          "2": "asked",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "was",
          "7": "him",
          "8": "any",
          "9": "he",
          "10": "been",
          "11": "question",
          "12": "what",
          "13": "had",
          "14": "have",
          "15": "known",
          "16": "be",
          "17": "it",
          "18": "to",
          "19": "places",
          "20": "being",
          "21": "not",
          "22": "avoid"
        },
        "answers":[[9,3,21,14,10,2,8,11,4,17,6,15,18,7,12,19,13,5,16,1],[9,3,21,14,10,2,8,11,4,17,6,15,5,7,12,19,13,18,16,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "They saw the storm coming",
        "words": {
          "4": "was",
          "1": "them",
          "3": "coming",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "seen",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "being",
          "8": "storm"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,4,5,3,6,1]]
    }
]